Guide to the North Carolina Farm Bureau Records
North Carolina Farm Bureau Records
- Legal and Legislative Material, 1962-1999; 11 linear feet
  - Legislative Materials
    - Peanut Legislation
      - 1995- General Information (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - 1995- General Information (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - 1995- General Information (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - 1995- Congressional Amendments (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - 1995- Congressional Amendments (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - 1995- Statistics (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - 1995- News Articles (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - 1995- Notes (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - 1996- General Information (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - 1996- General Information (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - 1996- General Information (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - 1996- Congressional Amendments (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - 1997- General Information (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - 1998- General Information (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Poultry Legislation
      - 1986 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - 1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - 1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - 1990 - 1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - 1993 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - 1994 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - 1995 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - 1996 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - 1997 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - 1998 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - 1998 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - 1998 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - 1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Tobacco Legislation
      - 1964- General Information (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - 1964- Statistics (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - 1968- General Information (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - 1970 - 1971- General Information (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - 1972- General Information (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - 1973- General Information (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - 1975- General Information (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - 1976- General Information (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - 1976- General Information (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - 1977- General Information (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - 1977- General Information (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - 1977- General Information (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - 1977- Statistics (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - 1977- News Articles (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - 1978- General Information (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - 1978- General Information (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - 1978- General Information (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - 1978- General Information (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - 1978- Statistics (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - 1978- News Articles (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - 1979- General Information (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - 1979- General Information (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - 1979- News Articles (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 1980- General Information (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - 1980- General Information (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - 1980- General Information (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - 1980- General Information (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - 1980- General Information (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - 1980- General Information (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - 1980- Statistics (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - 1980- News Articles (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - 1981- General Information (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - 1981- General Information (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - 1981- General Information (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - 1981- General Information (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - 1981- General Information (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - 1981- General Information (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - 1981- General Information (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - 1981- General Information (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - 1981- General Information (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - 1981- Statistics (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - 1981- News Articles (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - 1982- General Information (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - 1982- General Information (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - 1982- General Information (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - 1982- General Information (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - 1982- General Information (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - 1982- General Information (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - 1982- General Information (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - 1982- General Information (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - 1982- Congressional Bills (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - 1982- Statistics (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - 1982- News Articles (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - 1983- General Information (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - 1983- General Information (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - 1983- General Information (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - 1983- General Information (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - 1983- General Information (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - 1983- General Information (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - 1983- General Information (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - 1983- General Information (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - 1983- General Information (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - 1983- Congressional Bills (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - 1983- Statistics (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - 1983- Notes (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - 1983- News Articles (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - 1984- General Information (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - 1984- General Information (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - 1984- General Information (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - 1984- General Information (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - 1984- General Information (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - 1984- General Information (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - 1984- General Information (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - 1984- General Information (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - 1984- General Information (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - 1984- Statistics (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - 1984- Statistics (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - 1984- Notes (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - 1984- News Articles (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - 1985- Congressional Bills (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - 1985- Congressional Bills (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - 1985- Statistics (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - 1985- Notes (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - 1985- News Articles (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - 1985- News Articles (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - 1986- General Information (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - 1986- General Information (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - 1986- News Articles (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - 1986- Notes (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - 1987- General Information (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - 1987- Statistics (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - 1988- General Information (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - 1988- Statistics (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - 1988- News Articles (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - 1989- General Information (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - 1989- General Information (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - 1989- Legislative Amendments (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - 1989- Notes (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - 1989- News Articles (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - 1990- General Information (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - 1990- General Information (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - 1991- General Information (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - 1991- General Information (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - 1991- Congressional Bills (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - 1991- Statistics and Notes (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - 1992- General Information (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - 1992- General Information (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - 1993- General Information (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - 1993- General Information (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - 1993- General Information (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - 1993- General Information (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - 1993- Congressional Bills (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - 1993- Congressional Bills (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - 1993- Congressional Bills (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - 1993- Statistics (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - 1993- Statistics (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - 1993- Statistics (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - 1993- Notes (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - 1993- News Articles (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - 1993- News Articles (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - 1994- General Information (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - 1994- General Information (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - 1994- General Information (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - 1994- General Information (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - 1994- General Information (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - 1994- Statistics (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - 1994- Notes (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - 1994- News Articles (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - 1995- General Information (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - 1996- General Information (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - 1997- General Information (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Farm Bills
      - 1984- General Information (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - 1984- News Articles (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - 1985- General Information (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - 1985- News Articles (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - 1985- News Articles (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - 1996- General Information (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - 1996- General Information (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Legislation
      - Animal Rights, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Animal Rights, 1990 - 1991 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Animal Rights, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Animal Rights, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Animal Rights, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Animal Rights, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Animal Rights, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Animal Rights, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Animal Waste, 1995 - 1997 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Atrazine, Simazine, and Cyanazine, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Farmland Protection Bill, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Forestry, 1993 - 1996 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Fruits and Vegetables, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Fruits and Vegetables, 1993 - 1996 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Grain, 1981 - 1984 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Grain, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Grain, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Grain, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Grain, 1987 - 1988 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Grain, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Grain, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Grain, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Grain, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Grain, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Grain, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Grain, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Grain, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Grain, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Hops, 1975 - 1982 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Seed Protection, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Soybeans, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Soybeans, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Wheat (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Wetlands, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Financial Materials, 1940-1989; 7 linear feet
  Financial Materials includes records of membership dues for each county. The bulk of these records detail statistics from 1940-1970. Several original ledgers and bank registers of the organization are also included in this series. These ledgers have been split into four main subgroups: payments, disbursements, income, and receipts. In the case of many ledgers, the organization kept several records for a particular year, hence the overlapping dates for many of the ledgers.
  - Membership Dues (By County)
    - Alamance County (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Alexander County (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Allegheny County (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Anson County (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Ashe County (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Avery County (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Beaufort County (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Bertie County (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Bladen County (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Brunswick County (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Buncombe County (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Burke County (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Cabarrus County (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Caldwell County (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Camden County (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Carteret County (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Caswell County (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Catawba County (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Chatham County (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Cherokee County (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Chowan County (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Clay County (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Cleveland County (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Columbus County (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Craven County (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Cumberland County (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Currituck County (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Davidson County (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Davie County (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Duplin County (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Durham County (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Edgecombe County (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Forsyth County (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Franklin County (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Gaston County (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Gates County (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Graham County (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Granville County (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Greene County (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Guilford County (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Halifax County (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Harnett County (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Haywood County (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Henderson County (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Hertford County (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Hoke County (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Hyde County (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Iredell County (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Jackson County (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Johnston County (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Jones County (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Lee County (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Lenoir County (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Lincoln County (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - McDowell County (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Macon County (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Madison County (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Martin County (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Mecklenburg County (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Mitchell County (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Montgomery County (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Moore County (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Nash County (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - New Hanover County (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Northampton County (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Onslow County (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Orange County (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Pamlico County (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Pasquotank County (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Pender County (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Perquimons County (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Person County (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Pitt County (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Polk County (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Randolph County (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Richmond County (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Robeson County (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Rockingham County (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Rowan County (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Rutherford County (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Sampson County (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Scotland County (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Stanly County (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Stokes County (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Surry County (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Swain County (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Transylvania County (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Tyrell County (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Union County (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Vance County (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Wake County (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Warren County (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Washington County (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Watauga County (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Wayne County (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Wilkes County (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Wilson County (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Yadkin County (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Yancey County (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Membership Dues, 1940-1950 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Membership Dues, 1951-1960 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Membership Dues, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Membership Dues, 1966-1967 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Membership Dues, 1968-1970 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Financial Ledgers
    - Farm Bureau Payments
      - September, 1940 - February, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - August, 1945 - January, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - June, 1951 - August, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - June, 1951 - August, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - December, 1954 - August, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - September, 1959 - April, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - May, 1963 - November, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Farm Bureau Disbursements
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation, December, 1965 - August, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation, September, 1968 - December, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation, January, 1971 - December, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation, Fire Debentures, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Service Company, July, 1971 - December, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Marketing Association, June, 1963 - August, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Marketing Association, Swine Account, April, 1967 - July, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Marketing Association, Swine Account, June, 1967 - July, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Farm Bureau Income
      - January, 1955 - July, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - August, 1957 - December, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - April, 1960 - June, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - July, 1961 - September, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - September, 1962 - August, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - August, 1963 - July, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - July, 1964 - March, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - March, 1965 - November, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Farm Bureau Receipts
      - September, 1940 - February, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - April, 1951 - July, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - January, 1952 - December, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - January, 1959 - March, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - November, 1965 - August, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - August, 1966 - May, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - September, 1966 - November, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - May, 1967 - December, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - December, 1967 - August, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - September, 1971 - April, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Ledgers
      - R. Flake Shaw Memorial Scholarship Fund, January, 1965 - May, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - R. Flake Shaw Memorial Scholarship Fund, May, 1971 - March, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bank Registers
      - Farm Bureau News, Guilford National Bank (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Farm Bureau News, Guilford National Bank (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation, Bank of Greensboro (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation, Wachovia Bank and Trust Company (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Tobacco Associates, Inc., Bank of Greensboro (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Savings Account Passbooks and Registers (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Farm Bureau Casualty Register (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Farm Bureau Fire Register (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - American Farm Bureau Service Company, 1981-1989
    - Memoranda, Monthly Summary of Purchases, 1981-1989 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Reference Materials and Reports, 1965-1999; 8 linear feet
    Reference Materials and Reports reflect the wide body of research amassed by the Farm Bureau with regard to a variety of agricultural issues. Materials contain reports and publications produced by the North Carolina Farm Bureau and other national organizations. Publications are broken down by the publishing agency, such as the United States Department of Agriculture, the American Farm Bureau Federation, and the North Carolina Department of Agriculture. Publications are also grouped by subject matter when they refer to a certain agricutural topic such as cotton, peanuts, or tobacco. Materials grouped by subject matter come from a variety of publishing agencies, including internal reports to the North Carolina Farm Bureau and information from governmental, corporate, and non-profit organizations.
    - United States Department of Agriculture Reports
      - Acreage, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Agricultural Outlook, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Agricultural Outlook, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Agricultural Prices, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Agricultural Prices, March - May 1995 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Agricultural Prices, June - August 1995 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Agricultural Prices, September - December 1995 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Agricultural Prices, January - February 1996 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Agricultural Prices, March - April 1996 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Agricultural Prices, May - July 1996 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Agricultural Prices, August - December 1996 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Biotechnology News, January - June 1993 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Biotechnology News, July - December 1993 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Biotechnology News, May - August 1994 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Biotechnology News, September - December 1994 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Biotechnology News, January - April 1995 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Biotechnology News, May - December 1995 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Broilers, January - June 1993 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Broilers, July - December 1993 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Broilers, January - June 1994 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Broilers, July - December 1994 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Cattle and Sheep, 1995 - 1996 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Chemical Use- Fruits, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Chemical Use- General, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Chemical Use- Vegetables, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Cotton and Wool, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Cotton Ginnings, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Cotton Ginnings, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Cotton Ginnings, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Crop Production, 1995 (Summary) (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Crop Production, 1997 (Summary) (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Crop Production, July - September 1997 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Crop Production, October - December 1997 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Crop Production, January - April 1998 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Crop Production, May - July 1998 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Crop Production, August - October 1998 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Feed, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Grain, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Grain Stocks, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Grain Stocks, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Grain Stocks, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Grain Stocks, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Hogs, 1995 - 1996 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Livestock and Poultry, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Livestock and Poultry, 1994 - 1995 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Livestock and Poultry, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Livestock and Poultry, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Oil Crops, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Peanut Stocks, February - July 1996 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Peanut Stocks, August - December 1996 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Peanut Stocks, January - June 1997 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Peanut Stocks, July - December 1997 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Peanut Stocks, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Poultry Slaughter, 1995 - 1996 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Poultry Slaughter, January - June 1997 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Poultry Slaughter, July - December 1997 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Poultry Slaughter, January - April 1998 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Poultry Slaughter, May - October 1998 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Prospective Plantings, 1995 - 1996 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Prospective Plantings, 1997 - 1998 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Supply and Demand Estimates, August - October 1995 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Supply and Demand Estimates, November - December 1995 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Supply and Demand Estimates, January - March 1996 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Supply and Demand Estimates, July - September 1996 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Supply and Demand Estimates, October - December 1996 (Box 63, Folder 3)